(Sheldon:)So I guess you're really
holding up the other four fingers?
(Penny:)Oh, hey, what are you
doing here so early?
(Amy:)-Driving Sheldon to work.
-He's still mad at Leonard, huh?
(Amy:)He's mad at you, too.
(Amy:)He says you're the succubus
who led his friend astray.
(Stuart:)I don't know
what "succubus" is, but...
It has "suck" in it,
so that can't be good.
(Sheldon:)-Thought I heard you out here.
-Hey, Sheldon.
You don't get a "hey."
You get a "hmm."
(Penny:)Come on, don't be like that.
(Penny:)We had so much fun together
the last couple uf months.
(Sheldon:)You're right. Which makes your
betrayal all the more devastating.
(Leonard:)-Sheldon...
-I let you buy
(Sheldon:)feminine hygiene products
with my supermarket club card.
(Sheldon:)You have any idea the kind of coupons
I'm going to get in the mail now?
Sheldon, your Hght's with Leonard.
Penny's got nothing to do--
(Sheldon:)Careful, Amy.
(Sheldon:)The friend of my enemy's girlfriend
is my enemy.